{
    "subject": "resource/Callicarpa_longifolia",
    "predicate": "property/genus",
    "object": "Callicarpa",
    "human_readable": "The genus of Callicarpa longifolia is Callicarpa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886187314987183,
            "question": "Name the genus that includes Callicarpa longifolia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9881325364112854,
            "question": "Is Callicarpa the genus of Callicarpa longifolia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9868240356445312,
            "question": "If Callicarpa longifolia belongs to a genus called 'Callicarpa', what is that genus known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9861655235290527,
            "question": "What is the genus of Callicarpa longifolia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9810971021652222,
            "question": "To which genus does Callicarpa longifolia belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9792447090148926,
            "question": "What is the scientific name for the genus of Callicarpa longifolia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9622254371643066,
            "question": "Can you tell me the genus of this plant: Callicarpa longifolia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921860933303833,
            "question": "According to its classification, what group does Callicarpa longifolia belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.907537043094635,
            "question": "What is the botanical classification of Callicarpa longifolia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8559741377830505,
            "question": "What is the general category of organisms that Callicarpa longifolia belongs to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The genus of Callicarpa longifolia is Callicarpa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2703_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the botanical classification of Callicarpa longifolia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2703_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=According to its classification, what group does Callicarpa longifolia belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2703_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the genus of this plant: Callicarpa longifolia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2703_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2703_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The genus of Callicarpa longifolia is Callicarpa.\" For instance, one document mentions \"Callicarpa longifolia Lamarck,\" indicating that it belongs to the genus Callicarpa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}